- 嘿   - 嘿 你觉得如何
- Hey.     - Hey. So, what do you think?
新发型 项链 洋装 靴子 靴子
New haircut? Necklace? Dress? Boots? Boots!
它们比我平常买的靴子贵一点 也比租的贵
Yes! They're a little more than I usually spend on boots. Um, or rent.
天啊
Oh, my God.
- 我知道   - 我会怀念买得起食物的日子
- I know.     - I'll miss being able to afford food.
对不起 它们真的很漂亮 专柜小姐的表情像是在说
I'm sorry. They just looked so good. The saleswoman was like:
- "这些靴子太贵了 你买不起"   - 她说的对
- "These are too expensive for you."     - She had a point.
- 嘿   - 嗨 我的天啊
- Hey.     - Hi. Oh, my God.
- 摩妮卡 这双靴子好漂亮喔   - 它们是我的
- Oh, Monica, those boots are amazing!     - They're mine!
很遗憾我们得把它们退回去
Too bad we'll have to return them.
退回去 它们听得见你说话
Return them? Shh! They're gonna hear you.
我不会退回它们
I'm not returning them.
我知道它们很贵 但我会常常穿着它们 你会看到的
I know they cost a lot, but I'll wear them all the time. You'll see!
而且我喜欢听到赞美
Besides, I love the compliments.
你曾经拥有美到大家都想拥有的东西吗
Have you ever had something everyone wants?
- 我拥有你   - 说的好 这靴子我留定了
- I have you.     - Nice try. I'm keeping the boots.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
没错 我爱你
That's right. I love you.
我会一直跟你玩
And I'm gonna play with you all the time.
你怎么能让他对着你的胯下说话
How can you let him talk to your crotch like that?
- 他是在跟宝宝说话   - 原来如此
- He's talking to the baby.     - Oh! Okay.
好吧 因为当他说 "我等不及要听到你说第一句话"…
Okay. When he said, "I can't wait to hear your first words"...
我想"这招不错"
...I thought, "There's a trick."
我得走了 待会见
Okay, well I gotta go, you guys. I'll see you later.
- 好吧   - 拜拜
- Okay.     - Bye.
拜拜
Bye.
- 听着…   - 嗨
- Oh, hey, Rach. Um...     - Hi.
你能帮我一个忙吗 我妹妹知道你在罗夫·罗兰工作…
Can you do me a favor? My sister knows you work at Ralph Lauren...
算了 绝对不行 我不会再把罗夫·罗兰的衣服寄到监狱
Forget it! No way. I'm not sending more clothes to prison.
- 那是在暴殄天物   - 不 不是她
- It is a waste.     - No! Not her.
我最小的妹妹蒂娜对流行服装很有兴趣
My youngest sister, Dina. She's interested in fashion.
她想跟成功人士谈谈 给她一些建议
She wants to talk to someone successful to give her some advice.
- 我想我可以跟我的上司谈一谈   - 不 她想跟你谈
- I'll talk to my supervisor.     - No, no. She wants to talk to you.
真的吗 天啊 我是成功人士
Really? Oh, my God. I'm successful.
- 你能跟她见个面吗    - 我很乐意 请她来找我吧
- Would you meet with her?     - I'd love to. Have her come by.
天啊 你会喜欢她的 她是崔比亚尼家最聪明的孩子
Great. You'll love her. She's the smartest of all the Tribbiani children.
- 你知道学术评量测验吗    - 知道
- Yeah, you know the SATs?     - Yeah.
她有考过
She took them.
班念的是史密斯菲德小学吧
Hey, Ross, doesn't Ben go to Smithfield School?
对 怎么了
Yeah. Why?
- 史汀有个儿子在那里念书 - 我知道 他跟班是同班同学
- Sting has a son that goes there.     - I know. He's in Ben's class.
你知道却一直没有告诉我们
You knew and never said anything?
你只跟我们说那些笨恐龙的事
With all the stupid dinosaur stuff you tell us?
好吧 我不会再说恐龙的事 我能谈谈化石吗
Fine, no more dinosaur stuff. Can I talk about fossils?
"史汀七岁大的儿子" 还有他的照片
"Sting's son, 7." There's a picture.
你在看什么 "曼哈顿私立学校学童绑架指南"
What are you reading? "A Kidnapper's Guide to Manhattan Private Schools?"
我在看"纽约杂志" 报导城里最棒的学校
It's New York Magazine, an article about the best schools in the city.
- 你跟史汀很熟吗    - 事实上我没有见过他
- So how well do you know Sting?     - I haven't met him.
真的很糟糕 我很想去听他星期五的演唱会 但票卖完了
Uh-huh. That's too bad. I wanna go to his concert Friday, but it's sold out.
我知道了 你为什么不去跟他要票
I know! Why don't you meet him and get tickets?
如果你可以要到两张 我就带你去
If you get two, I'll take you.
明天我会去接班 或许他会在那里
I'm picking Ben up tomorrow. Maybe he'll be there.
好吧 你真是幸运 明天你可能就会看到史汀了
There you go. Ugh, you're so lucky. You might meet Sting tomorrow.
所以人一定要生小孩
That's why you have kids.
- 嗨 大伙们   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hey.
嗨 摩妮卡 嗨 靴子
Hi, Monica. Hi, boots.
看吧 钱德 我常常穿它们 它们真的很实用
See? I'm getting a lot of use out of them already.
它们可以搭配洋装 裙子 长裤…
They're very practical. You can wear them with dresses, skirts, pants...
你可以穿着它们搭配的短裤站在街角 赚点钱来付帐单
Wear them with shorts on the corner and earn money to pay for them.
- 哇 它们好漂亮   - 它们真的很磨脚
- Wow, they're beautiful.     - They hurt so much.
- 什么    - 做这双靴子的人…
- What?     - The guy who made these...
一定很讨厌脚 想要看到它们死掉
...hates feet and wants to see them die.
把它们送给我 我的脚好几年没有感觉了
Give them to me. I haven't felt my feet in years.
不行 我告诉钱德我会一直穿着它们
I can't. I spent so much on them, and told Chandler I'd wear them all the time.
- 我不能把它们送人   - 你可以拿去退货换钱
- I can't just give them away.     - Then get your money back, return them.
我也不能那么做
I can't do that either.
脚跟的地方有磨损 内衬沾满了我的血
The soles are scuffed up, and the insides are filled with my blood.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 我刚刚去学校接班   - 噢
- Hey, I, uh, just picked up Ben from school.     - Oh.
你的任务还没完成吧
I don't think you did a very thorough job.
我把他送回卡萝家了
I dropped him off at Carol's.
总之 我没有要到门票
Anyway, I'm not gonna get those tickets.
不 为什么
Oh, no. Why not?
结果班跟史汀的儿子处得不好
Well, it turns out Ben and Sting's son do not get along.
- 怎么会呢    - 很明显地史汀的儿子取笑…
- How come?     - Apparently, Sting's son made fun...
班的妈妈们是女同志
...of the fact that Ben's moms are "les-be-nims."
等一下 如果他们处不好 帮他们劝和
Wait! If they don't get along, you should smooth things over.
- 让他们做好朋友   - 你不能逼孩子们做朋友
- Make them be friends.     - You can't force kids to be friends.
当然可以 给他们一些积木 让他们在游戏床里玩
Sure you can. Give them some blocks. Put them in a playpen.
- 游戏床 班七岁了   - 你的小孩七岁了
- Playpen? Ben's 7.     - Your kid is 7?
他真的很矮喔
He's really small.
- 拜托你去要门票   - 抱歉 我办不到
- Please! Please get the tickets.     - I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
- 不 你可以 史汀他自己说的   - 什么
- Yes, you can. Sting says so himself.     - What?
罗斯可以
Ross can!
听着 我很抱歉…
Look, Pheeb, I'm sorry...
罗斯可以
Ross can!
菲比
Phoebe?
罗斯可以帮我拿到门票
Ross can get me the tickets!
她来了 未来的流行界超级巨星
Here she is. Future fashion superstar.
- 乔伊 我真的…   - 我的妹妹蒂娜
- Oh, Joey, I'm hardly...     - My little sister, Dina!
- 蒂娜 很高兴见到你   - 嗨
- Right. Hi, Dina. Nice to meet you.     - Hi.
谢谢你答应见我 乔伊告诉我很多关于你的事
Thanks for meeting me. Joey's told me so much about you.
她好兴奋喔
This is exciting for her.
我让你们两个"流行大师"
Well, I'll let you two fash...
坐下来好好谈正事
...ists get down to business.
好吧 蒂娜
Okay. All right, Dina.
我们来谈谈 你可以考虑的…
Let's talk about the different areas of fashion...
服装界的不同领域
...you could get involved in.
让我看看 有设计部门 但那得需要相关文凭
Let's see. There's design. But you may need another degree for that.
销售部门不错 你可以旅行
Uh, there's sales, which is great. You get to travel.
我不在乎流行服装 我怀孕了
I don't care about fashion! I'm pregnant.
我知道你也是 你得帮帮我
And I know you are too, so you gotta help me.
还有行销部门
And there's marketing.
- 怎么了    - 没事 我只是在打哈欠
- What's wrong?     - Oh, nothing. I'm just... I just was yawning.
别忘了今晚我公司要办派对
Don't forget my office holiday party tonight.
我们今晚不一定要去 对吧
We don't really have to go tonight, do we?
我知道你不喜欢参加我公司的派对
Sweetie, I know that you don't like my office parties.
但你可以穿你的新靴子
But you can wear your new boots.
看吧 每件事都有它好的一面
See? Every cloud has a supple leather lining.
- 今晚我不想穿靴子   - 为什么
- I don't wanna wear the boots tonight.     - Why not?
我担心你老板看到它们会觉得他们给你的薪水太高了
I'm worried your bosses might see them and think they pay you too much money.
或是你的助理看到它们会要求加薪
Or your assistant will see them and want a raise.
你以为我是在帮靴子订价的公司上班吗
Do you think I work at a boot-pricing company?
我已经挑好了我要穿的衣服 靴子跟它不配
Anyway, I picked an outfit, and the boots don't go with it.
你说过这双靴子
You said you paid all that money...
可以搭配裙子 洋装跟长裤
...because those boots go with skirts, dresses and pants.
好吧 如果你要的话 我会穿靴子
Fine, if you want me to wear the boots, I'll wear the boots.
事实上我要到卧室去试穿我的衣服
In fact, I'll go in to my room now and try the outfit on.
- 好吧   - 好吧
- Okay.     - Okay.
穿着我的靴子参加圣诞节派对
Christmas party in my boots!
我不能进去 我不敢告诉他
I can't go in there. I can't tell him.
一定会没事的 他一直都非常支持我
It'll be okay. He's been incredibly supportive of me.
如果他大发脾气 快把肉饼潜艇三明治拿给他
And if he gets a little upset, that's what the meatball sub is for.
- 谢谢   - 好吧
- Thank you.     - Okay.
我的流行界女王们回来了
Hey! It's my fashion girls!
- 怎么了    - 你为什么不坐下呢
- What's wrong?     - Why don't you sit down?
蒂娜有件事想告诉你
Dina has something that she wants to tell you.
发生了什么事 是妈妈吗
Oh. What's going on? Is it Mom?
她生病了吗 是爸爸的心脏吗 那是三明治吗
Is she sick? Is it Dad's heart? Is that a sandwich?
- 妈妈跟爸爸没事   - 那是三明治吗
- Joe, Mom and Dad are fine.     - Is that a sandwich?
乔伊 有件事你得知道 蒂娜
Joey, there's something that you should know. Dina?
- 我怀孕了   - 什么
- I'm pregnant.     - What?
快给他三明治
Now. Give him the sandwich. Give him the sandwich!
很明显地这是个误会 你不可能怀孕
Obviously, this is a mistake. You can't be pregnant.
因为你得先做爱才会怀孕
You have to have sex to get pregnant.
乔伊 我试着学你一样 等到25岁再尝禁果
Joe, I tried to wait until I was 25, like you did.
- 什么 蒂娜…   - 小家伙
- What? Dina...     - Bub!
我不敢相信 你念过大学 你是个好孩子
I can't believe this! You're the good one. You went to college.
还念了两年
Both years!
- 是谁干的   - 巴比·科索 但他是个很好的人
- Who did this to you?     - Bobby Corso. But he's a real nice guy.
我很喜欢他 他很好笑
I like him a lot. He's real funny.
你因为"好笑"而怀孕
You got pregnant for "funny"?
蒂娜 如果他很好笑 你只要笑就行了
Dina, if he's funny, laugh!
- 我马上回来 你留在这里   - 为什么 你要去哪里
- I'll be back in a while. Stay here!     - Why? Where are you going.
我现在没办法看你
I can't look at you right now.
我知道
I know.
你在这里啊 班
Oh, there you are, Ben.
菲比阿姨 你来这里做什么
Aunt Phoebe, what are you doing here?
我听说你跟一个同学处不好
I heard you have a problem with a boy in your class.
我想来帮你们冷静下来
And so I thought I'd just come down here...
好好地谈一谈 解决所有问题
...I'd sit you both down, have a talk and make it all okay.
那个孩子叫做史汀的儿子
Now, um, the boy's name is Sting's son.
杰克 我恨他 他是个混蛋
Jack? I hate him. He's a jerk.
有时候人们外表看起来像是混蛋…
Now, Ben, sometimes people may seem like jerks on the outside...
但他们有个名人爸爸
...but they have famous fathers.
我得走了 我朋友道格在等我
I have to go. My friend Doug is waiting for me.
你跟他做朋友
Him you're friends with.
对不起 需要我帮忙吗
Excuse me, can I help you with something?
对 我在找杰克的父母
Yes. Yes you can. I'm looking for Jack's parents.
- 你是家长吗    - 我来找班
- Are you with a student?     - Uh-huh. I'm with Ben.
- 你是班的妈妈    - 我是班的妈妈
- Are you one of Ben's mothers?     - I am one of Ben's mothers.
我是女同志
I'm a lesbian.
我爸妈很难接受这种事
It was difficult coming out to my parents.
嗨 我是珍妮·布恩 我是新来的老师
Heh, well, hi. I'm Jenny Boon. I'm the new teacher here.
- 噢   - 我只见过你的另一半 卡萝
- Oh.     - I've only met your partner, Carol.
那么我就是苏珊
Ah! Okay, that would make me Susan.
对 你要找杰克父母
Right. Are you looking for Jack's parents to discuss...
讨论他跟班的问题吗
...the problems he's having with Ben? Yeah.
我想父母们应该坐下来好好谈一谈
I think the parents should sit down together and converse.
对 我们就那么办吧
Yeah, let's do that!
听起来很不错 我们应该坐下来谈一谈
That sounds good. We should sit and talk.
我 我的爱人卡萝跟史汀夫妇
Just me, my lover, Carol, and the Stings.
- 我要怎么联络他们    - 联络簿上有他们的电话号码
- How will I get in touch with them?     - Their number's on the contact sheet.
我能影印一份吗 卡萝把它丢了 她弄丢了我们的联络簿
Uh-huh. Um, could I get a copy of that? Carol threw it out. She lost ours.
她真的很糊涂 但天啊 她的屁股真的很好看
She's such a scatterbrain. But, man, what a hot piece of ass.
- 那场派对还不错   - 对 我不知道还有舞会
- That wasn't bad.     - I didn't know there'd be dancing.
那是个大惊喜
That was a fun surprise!
- 我看不到计程车 或许我们该走路 - 不 我们不能走路
- I don't see any, uh, cabs. We should walk.     - No, we can't walk.
- 离地铁站只有15条街远 来吧   - 好吧
It's, like, 15 blocks to the subway. Let's go.
你想我们可以从那个下水道孔直接掉到地铁站里吗
Do you think we can get to the subway if we climb through that manhole cover?
- 什么事不对劲吗    - 我走不动了 好吗
- What's going on?     - I can't walk, okay? Okay?
- 买这双靴子是个天大的错误   - 什么
- These boots were a huge mistake.     - What?
你说的对 我不该买下它们
You were right. I never should've bought them.
它们害我的脚好痛 我的脚趾快断了
They're killing me, one toe at a time.
我说的对 感觉才是最重要的
I was right. This is what it feels like to be right.
我为什么觉得很不安
It's oddly unsettling.
我们要怎么回家  我们来玩骑马打仗吧
How are will gonna get home? Maybe a piggyback ride?
- 来吧   - 好吧 等一下
- Hop on.     - Okay, wait. Give me a second.
我先把靴子脱掉
Let me just get my boots off first.
天啊
Oh, God.
我知道你很痛 但我有点心痒痒的
Honey, I know you're in pain right now, but I'm a little turned on.
你会不会担心走路的时候 宝宝会掉出来
Do you worry that you'll be walking and your baby will slip out?
你念哪所大学的 蒂娜
What college was that, Dina?
天啊 巴比
Oh, my God! Bobby?
蒂娜 很高兴能见到你
Hi, Dina. Good to see you.
- 乔伊 你在做什么    - 我只是在做我该做的事
- Joey, what are you doing?     - Just what needs to be done.
- 亲爱的亲友们 我们齐聚一堂…   - 这太疯狂了
- Dearly beloved, we're gathered here...     - Ugh, Joey, this is crazy.
我在跟上帝说话 别打断我
Don't interrupt me when I'm talking to God!
- 我们说到哪里了 你愿意嫁这个人…   - 不
- Where were we? Do you take this man...?     - No!
- 你得嫁他   - 不 我不会的
- Oh, you'll take him.     - No I won't!
- 你没有权利说话   - 不 我有
- Hey, you don't get a say.     - Yes I do.
我听到了 已经完成一半 再来是你
Ah, I heard "I do." We're halfway there. Okay, you.
好吧 乔伊 够了
All right, Joey, that is enough!
虽然这个婚礼既漂亮又温馨 这是不合法的
Listen, as beautiful and moving as this ceremony is, this is not legal.
他们没有结婚证书或证婚人
They don't have a marriage license, they don't have witnesses...
而且新郎只穿一只鞋
...and the groom only has on one shoe.
对 他把另一只鞋脱了 用它来打我
Yeah, he took the other one off and hit me with it.
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
你应该了解他们是成年人 可以自己做决定
You're supposed to realize they are adults and can make their own decisions.
不 他们不能 他们笨到让自己怀孕
No, they can't. They're stupid enough to get knocked up!
嘿
Hey!
预防措施不一定有效 对吧
Contraceptives are not always effective. Right?
- 对 我们没有做预防措施   - 孩子们 帮帮我吧
- Yeah. We kind of didn't use any.     - Oh, come on, kids, a little help here.
这个地方真的很棒
Wow! This place is incredible!
史汀的笔 他送给了菲比
Sting's pen. That he gave to Phoebe.
来吧 秘密通道
Come on, secret passageway.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
我是楚蒂 你一定是班的妈妈
I'm Trudie. You must be Ben's mum.
不然我为什么要到这里来呢
Why else would I be here?
请坐
Why don't you sit down?
我知道杰克跟班最近处得不太好
I gather Jack and Ben haven't been getting along.
- 对   - 我相信这个故事一定有两面说法
- Yeah.     - I'm sure there are two sides to this.
但我听到的是班是个"大笨蛋"
But all I've heard is that Ben's a bit of a "poo-poo head."
抱歉 杰克的爸爸不会来吗
Um, I'm sorry. Won't Jack's father be joining us?
对不起 杰克的爸爸没空
I'm sorry, Jack's father's not available.
好吧
Mm-hm. Okay.
好吧 我们可以再约 星期五晚上八点见吗
Well then could we reschedule for Friday night, perhaps at 8:00?
不 我想那是行不通的 我丈夫要办演唱会
Oh, no, that wouldn't work. My husband's in concert.
演唱会 对 那让问题变得有点棘手
Concert. Yeah. Mm. That just put us in quite a pickle.
演唱会前后我都有事
Because I'm very busy before and after the concert...
演唱会的时间他又很忙
...and he's obviously busy during.
我想你跟我现在该来谈谈杰克跟班的事
So you and I should talk about Jack and Ben now.
除非…
Unless... Unless, um...
我愿意到演唱会上…
Okay, I would be willing to go to the concert...
想一想孩子们的事
...um, all the while thinking about the children of course.
- 你是来要票的吗    - 谢谢 四张就够了
- Are you here for tickets?     - Ugh, thanks. Four would be great.
我不会把演唱会门票送给这样利用自己孩子的人
I'm not giving tickets to someone who'd use their son like this.
那正好 班不是我的儿子
Oh, then you're in luck. Ben's not my son.
听着 我已经按下静声警铃
Look, I've pressed a button triggering an alarm.
- 警察随时会到   - "警察合唱团"要来
- Any minute now, the police will be here.     - The Police? Here?
他们要复合了
A reunion? Ooh!
好吧 已经走了十条街 只剩五条
Okay, 10 blocks down, five to go.
- 等一下 停   - 抱歉 你需要休息吗
- Oh, wait! Stop!     - Oh, I'm sorry. Do you need a break?
是米色的靴子 你能靠近一点让我看看价钱吗
My boots in tan! Get closer so I can see the price.
我在这里就看到了 它会害得你丢掉一个老公
I can see it from right here. It'll cost you one husband.
抱歉 我可以自己走了 把我的靴子还给我
Okay, I think I can walk the rest of the way now. Just give me my boots.
- 我没有拿你的靴子   - 我也没拿 它们在哪里
- I don't have your boots.     - I don't either. Where are they?
你为什么不看看马鞍
Why don't you check in one of my saddlebags...
我先去吃点草
...while I chew on a bale of hay?
好吧 天啊 我们得回去找靴子
Okay. My God, we gotta go back and get them!
你会再穿那双靴子吗
Are you seriously ever gonna wear the boots again?
好吧 我再也不会穿它们 我只是没机会跟它们说再见
Okay, I'll never wear them again. I didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
你知道吗 你可以跟米色的靴子说再见
Know what? You can say goodbye to the tan ones.
- 好吧   - 好吧
- Okay. All right. Unh.     - Okay.
再见 靴子 等一下 打五折
Bye, boots. Wait! Half off!
他们没结婚 不
Joey, because they're not getting married...
代表那是世界末日
...doesn't mean this is a disaster.
- 或许他们有计划   - 好吧 我们听听他们的计划
- Maybe they have a plan.     - Oh. Oh! Okay, let's hear their plan.
蒂娜跟巴比会有什么样的未来
What's the future look like for Dina and Bobby?
这个嘛 我对我的乐团寄望很高
Well, I really have high hopes for my band.
你说的对 他是很好笑
You were right. He is funny.
等一下 我敢说一开始告诉大家你要当演员 大家都笑你
Wait! I bet when you told people you wanted to act, they laughed at you.
来吧 巴比 跟我们谈谈你的乐团
Bobby, tell us a little about your band.
团员只有我跟我朋友鲁斯特 乐团名字叫做"呆瓜"
It's just me and my pal, Rooster. The band's name is Numbnuts.
真的吗
Really?
如果你要生孩子 你应该结婚
Dina, if you're having a baby, you should be married.
即使是嫁给巴比 我不是在夸奖你
Even if it is to Bobby. Dude, that's not a compliment.
- 我就知道你不会支持我   - 你打算怎么办
- I knew you wouldn't be supportive.     - What are you gonna do?
你要自己带大孩子 没有丈夫帮你
You're gonna have the baby and raise it by yourself, without a husband?
你没办法当单亲妈妈 你会毁了自己的一生
You can't be a single mother alone! You're gonna ruin your life!
- 对不起 我毁了我的一生吗    - 不 你不一样
- Excuse me. Am I ruining my life?     - No, no, it's different for you.
你很坚强
You're strong and together.
你不是不知道自己在做什么的笨小孩
You're not some dumb kid who doesn't know what she's doing.
- 你说什么    - 我一次只能跟一个孕妇说话
- Excuse me?     - One pregnant woman at a time, please!
我只是希望你过得好
I just want you to be okay.
逼她嫁给巴比 她就会过的好吗
Forcing her to marry Bobby is gonna make that happen?
或许吧
Maybe.
对 "呆瓜"的音乐是什么类型的…
Yeah. So, uh, what kind of music does Numbnuts...?
算了 我办不到
Ah, forget it! I can't!
我真的很害怕
Joey, I am scared to death about this.
但我想我办得到 我只是需要帮助
But I think I can do it. I just need some help.
- 巴比会一直陪着我   - 没错
- And Bobby's gonna be here the whole time.     - You bet I am.
至于你刚刚问的那个问题 我们唱纯黑帮饶舌歌
To answer your earlier question, we're straight-up gangster rap.
瑞秋告诉我 你一直都很支持她
Rachel's told me how much easier you've made this on her.
- 你为什么不能支持我    - 因为…
- Why can't you do that for me?     - Because!
因为你是我的妹妹
Because you're my baby sister!
你是我哥哥
And you're my big brother.
你是我全世界最喜欢的人
I mean, you're my favorite guy in the whole world.
我甚至不怕告诉妈妈跟爸爸 我害怕告诉你
I'm not even scared to tell Mom and Dad. I was scared of telling you.
我也会怕他们 但好吧
I'd be scared of them, but all right.
想到你会因为我怀孕而生我的气 我就受不了
I can't stand the thought of having this baby with you mad at me.
我要他有舅舅
I want him to have his uncle.
我的宝宝会有乔伊舅舅吗
Is my baby gonna have his Uncle Joey?
他当然会有乔伊舅舅
Of course he's gonna have his Uncle Joey.
我们会没事的 即使我们没结婚 宝宝还是会得到宠爱
We'll be all right. Even if we're not married, this baby is gonna be so loved.
- 不只是我们会爱他   - 没错
- And not just by us.     - That's right.
- 他的舅舅也会爱他   - 还有你
- By his uncle too.     - And by you.
巴比 我们为什么不过来这里让他们独处一下
Okay, Bobby, come over here and let them have a little moment, okay?
过来
Come here!
不 说真的 你到底有什么问题
No, seriously, what's wrong with you?
你一定会很爱我 我弄到史汀的门票了
You're gonna love me so much. I got Sting tickets!
天啊 我真的爱你 你怎么办到的
Oh, my God, I do love you! How did you do it?
就说
Well, let's just say:
罗斯可以
Ross can!
- 座位是哪一区    - 在中间包厢
- Where are the seats?     - Middle balcony.
我们的位置 离史汀他太太…
Would you say that that's more than 50 yards away...
跟他的家人超过50码吗
...from Sting, his wife, or a member of his family?
- 对   - 那样就不犯法
- Yeah.     - Then that's not breaking the law!
我会去
I'm there!